window.IELTS_QUESTION_BANK = {
  test1_section1: {
    title: "IELTS Listening Test 1 – Section 1",
    audio: "https://www.yayastudio.us/public/audio/Listening_Test_1_SECTION_1.mp3",

    questions: [
      {
        number: 1,
        type: "blank",
        question: "Child’s Name:",
        answer: "Ethan Park"
      },
      {
        number: 2,
        type: "blank",
        question: "Age:",
        answer: "9"
      },
      {
        number: 3,
        type: "blank",
        question: "Programme Start Date:",
        answer: "July 14th"
      },
      {
        number: 4,
        type: "blank",
        question: "Basic Fee:",
        answer: "$480"
      },
      {
        number: 5,
        type: "blank",
        question: "Meal Plan Fee:",
        answer: "$60"
      },
      {
        number: 6,
        type: "blank",
        question: "Allergy Information:",
        answer: "peanuts"
      },
      {
        number: 7,
        type: "choice",
        question: "Which programme is suitable for Ethan?",
        options: ["Adventure Camp", "Explorer Camp", "Science Camp"],
        answer: 1
      },
      {
        number: 8,
        type: "choice",
        question: "How long does the programme last?",
        options: ["One week", "Two weeks", "Three weeks"],
        answer: 1
      },
      {
        number: 9,
        type: "choice",
        question: "How will the woman pay?",
        options: ["By credit card", "By bank transfer", "In cash"],
        answer: 1
      },
      {
        number: 10,
        type: "choice",
        question: "What will the woman receive after completing the online form?",
        options: ["A confirmation letter", "A payment receipt", "An email containing bank details"],
        answer: 2
      }
    ]
  }
};
